# DENISE FOSTER 14827 Mora Drive Baton Rouge, La 70809 225.278.2351

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am looking for a fulfilling career, working in a clinical or laboratory setting. I have over 5 years of experience working in a hospital setting as a Sr. Phlebotomist and Medical Lab Assistant. I love what I do and I am looking for a job where I can become rooted.

#### **EDUCATION**

Our Lady of the Lake College, Baton Rouge La. Graduated in 2008.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

2008 - Present

#### Sr. Phlebotomist

Our Lady of the Lake Regional Medical Center 5000 Hennessey Drive, Baton Rouge, La

- collect specimen on patients ranging from infants to geriatrics, along with assisting nursing staff with activated clotting times for heart-stent, patients
- maintain records of tests performed, access information using Cerner
- train lower level phlebotomist
- dispatch lab orders to phlebotomist and clear a pending of patients and prepare forms for record keeping for the next shift
- concentration in the intensive care units, and cover areas of missed patients

### 2007 - 2008

Resolution Specialist

Convergys

Baton Rouge, La

• assist customers with billing questions, update plans, and sales

## 1995 - 2007

# Hair Stylist/Self employed

Baton Rouge, La

- specialized in hair color and cuts in charge of marketing, bookkeeping
- product sales, and educated clients about hair care